(角都)火遁 頭刻苦！
Fire Style: Searing Migraine!
He can even use the Fire Style?
《カカシ : 火遁まで…！》
Choji! Ino! You guys okay?
(シカマル)チョウジ！ いの！ 大丈夫か!?
Yes!
(いの)えぇ。
(チョウジ)うわ…！ うん。
Yeah...!
(飛段)キエーッ！
やるな… やっぱ。
You're pretty good, just as I thought...
Kakashi Sensei!
カカシ先生！
(いの)大丈夫ですか!?
(カカシ)あぁ。
Are you okay?
Yeah...
《とはいっても
写輪眼を使ったまま➡
That being said,
I've used four Lighting Blade shots
while using the Sharingan...
雷切を４発…
グズグズは してられないな》
I can't be sitting idly by.
アイツら… うまく
連携を使ってくるわね。
They're using really good combos.
さっきの カカシ先生の雷切
絶対 当たってたのに➡
And here Kakashi Sensei definitely
nailed him with the Lightning Blade...
なんで 死なないの!? アイツ。
Why won't he die?
I'm sure I crushed his heart.
He really should be dead.
あぁ…。 確実に 心臓を潰した。
本来なら 死んでるはずだ。
だが 倒せたのは ヤツの体から
出てきた バケモノのうちの１匹…。
But what I killed was one
of the monsters
that came out of his body.
ソイツが ヤツの本体の代わりに
死んだと考えられる。
We can assume that it died
in place of his real body.
さっき ヤツが 影真似手裏剣を➡
It was the same when he broke
my Shadow Possession Shuriken Jutsu...
外して逃げたときもそうだったが
本体から 切り離した腕に➡
Something that looked like
a heart was attached
心臓のようなものが ついていて
自律して 行動した。
to the arm that had been
separated from his body
and it was moving on its own.
それって どういうこと？
What...does that mean?
おそらく ヤツ本体を含め
体から出てきた バケモノそれぞれに➡
If you include his real body,
each monster that came out of his body
has a heart, and they are all his.
心臓があり
そのすべてが ヤツのもの。
つまり ヤツには
心臓が５つあるってことだ。
In other words,
it means he probably has five hearts.
えっ!?
そんなことって！
What?!
How can he...?
今 先生の雷切で １つ減ったがな。
However, he lost one of them to
Sensei's Lightning Blade just now, though.
じゃあ アイツを完全に
やっつけるには➡
Then that means we have
to crush his other four hearts
あと４つの心臓を
潰さなきゃならないってこと？
in order to take him out completely?
あぁ。
Yeah...
You're very perceptive.
That's exactly right...
よく 気づいたな。 そのとおり。
この それぞれの心臓は
かつて戦って奪い取った➡
I took each of these hearts
from Shinobi I once fought.
忍たちのものだ。
また 補充はきく。
I can always replenish my stock...
お前らの心臓でな。
with your hearts.
《なるほど…。 他者の心臓を➡
I get it...
By connecting his Chakra Network
to the others' hearts,
経絡系に宿っている チャクラ性質ごと
取りこんだのか…。
he incorporates their Chakra natures
as well, huh?
どうりで
いくつもの性質変化を…》
No wonder he's able to
use several different natures.
ところでよぉ 木ノ葉って
死んだら 土葬？
By the way, does the Hidden Leaf Village
bury their dead?
土葬だったら
めんどくせぇんだよ。
Burials are a pain in the neck, you see.
賞金首 掘り起こして
換金するぞ とか➡
I bet Kakuzu's going to say,
"We're going to dig up the body
and exchange him for money."
角都 言い出しそうだし…。
あ～ あのヒゲ野郎。
And here I thought I could have
some fun with that bearded jerk...
ちょいとは
楽しませてくれると思って➡
期待したのによぉ…。
やっぱ たいしたことねえし！
He was nothing special, after all.
首をはねられたクセに よく言う…。
You're one to talk, especially since
you got your head chopped off...
うるせぇ だまってろ!!
Shut up. You keep quiet!
お前ら 敵討ちのつもりだろうが
そんな程度じゃ ムリ ムリ！
I'm sure you guys are intent
on revenge.
But you guys are too weak for that.
ガキどもは 見た感じ
アイツの教え子ってとこか？
You all look like kids.
I guess you were his students, huh?
まぁ
あんな カスに教わってたんじゃ➡
Well, with scum like him as your teacher,
you won't amount to much.
たかが知れてるがな…。
アスマ先生を悪く言うな！
(シカマル)チョウジ…。
Don't insult Asuma Sensei!
Choji.
(飛段)ふ～ん。
美しきは師弟愛ってか？
Beautiful loving bonds between
student and teacher, huh?
ヘッ バカらしい。
Heh, how stupid!
キサマ…！
チョウジ！
You jerk...!
Choji!
あんな クソ野郎の
どこがいいんだ？
What's so great about an idiot like that?
デーブ！
うぬぬ…。
Fatty?!
うお～!!
(いの)チョウジ！
Choji!
ハッ。
フン！
うお～！
ハハ～！ ヒャッホウ！
はぁ…。
バカ野郎 あんな見え見えの挑発に
のってどうする！
You idiot!
What's the point of getting stirred up
by such an obvious trick?!
ご… ごめん…。
あ！
I-I'm sorry...
うん？ …はっ うお～！
うわ～！
チョウジ！
Choji!
ヒャッホウ！
ヒョー！
《このままでは…》
At this rate...
死ね。
Die.
小娘。
Little girl...
シカマル！
Shikamaru!
うう…。
ぐわぁ…。
雑魚どもが。
You small fries.
死ね。
Die.
ぐあっ。
ヒャッホ～！
ハハ…。
テメエも終わりだ。
It's over for you, too.
はぁ!?
WATER
あ～あ。
Oh, boy.
はぁ… だっせぇ…。
How pathetic...
(シカマル)大丈夫か？
(チョウジ)う うん。
You okay?
Y-Yeah...
(いの)なんとか…。
Somehow.
だっせぇな おい…
なんだ そのザマ。
You're pathetic, man.
What a disgrace.
キサマこそ 影分身に気づかないとは。
You, too. How could you not realize
it was a Shadow Clone?
ありゃりゃ… 見てた？
Uh-oh... You saw that?
(カカシ)シカマル… どう戦う？
Shikamaru... How shall we fight?
引き離しましょう アイツら２人を。
Let's separate those two.
そして 個別に攻めるのが
得策っすね。
Our best plan would be to
attack them separately.
Yeah.
(シカマル)
ヤツらの 連携攻撃を封じたうえで➡
After we eliminate their ability
to do combo attacks,
あと４回殺せば倒せるほうを
先に 集中攻撃。
we'll focus on destroying
his four remaining hearts.
(カカシ)だとすると
あの飛段ってヤツを➡
If we're going to do that,
we'll need someone to stall Hidan...
足止めする役が 必要ってわけか。
私がやる！ 私が 今
いちばん チャクラを温存してるし➡
I'll do it!
I have the most Chakra
stored up right now.
それに シンプルな戦闘じゃ
役に立てないから➡
And I won't be of much use
in straight attacks...
心転身の術で。
ダメだ！
I'll use my Mind Transfer Jutsu...
No! The Mind Transfer is
primarily a Combo Jutsu
心転身は そもそも オレの影真似で
相手の動きを止めてから使う➡
used after stopping an opponent's movements
with my Shadow Possession.
連携術だぞ！
If you miss,
はずしたら 数分間は
自分の体に戻れない。
you won't be able to return to
your own body for several minutes.
リスクが高すぎる！
It's too risky!
オレがやる！
I'll do it.
- Huh?
- What?!
影真似で縛ってから引き離す。
We'll separate them after I restrain him
with my Shadow Possession Jutsu.
だが どうやって縛るかだな。
But how do you plan on restraining him?
どちらにしろ 陽動はいるぞ。
We'll need a diversion, either way.
Then I'll take care of that.
なら その役は ボクが！
それも ダメだ！
That won't do, either!
You'll be finished if he attacks you
and gets even a little of your blood.
ヤツの攻撃を少しでも受け
血を取られたら 終わりなんだぞ。
It'll be just like before.
さっきもそうだが
ヤツに こっちから近づいて➡
It'd be a bad move for us to
approach him and attack!
攻撃すること自体 ズレてる！
チョウジ！ お前は カカシ先生と一緒に➡
Choji.
You store up Chakra to take out
the masked guy with Kakashi Sensei.
マスクのヤツをやるために
チャクラを温存しとけ！
うん！
Right!
アイツは オレ１人で捕まえる。
I'll capture him by myself.
そして あの役は オレがやる。
And...
I'll fulfill that role!
I'll capture him by myself.
(シカマル)アイツは オレ１人で捕まえる！
そして あの役は オレがやる！
And...
I'll fulfill that role!
わかった。 シカマルに任せよう。
Got it. I'll leave it to you, Shikamaru.
Take this.
これを。
あぁ。
Right...
うん？
はっ！ またそれか！
That again?!
そんなにオレの鎌と能力が怖いか！
あっ？
Are you that afraid of my powerful scythe?
I'm your opponent.
お前の相手は オレだ！
Hey-hey-hey!
おいおい おいおい！
Sneaking around like that from a distance?
離れたとこから コソコソと！
情けねえ!!
How pathetic!
(飛段)遅いぜ！
Too slow!
What--?!
《飛段 : 影で拾って投げたのか？》
He picked it up...
and threw it with his shadow?!
空中なら 身動きがとれない！
He can't move in midair!
もらった!!
He's ours!
けっ… 甘いぜ。
You wish!
影にだけ注意してりゃ
こんな術なんざ くだらん…。
If I just focus on the shadow,
a Jutsu like this is worthless!
What?
(飛段)なに!?
離れたとこから
コソコソだけじゃねえぜ！
I'm not just sneaking around
from a distance!
影真似の術 成功。
The Shadow Possession Jutsu
is a success.
この野郎…。
You...jerk!
いけ！ シカマル！
Go, Shikamaru!
(チョウジ)こっちは任せて！
(いの)頼んだわよ！
Leave this to us!
We're counting on you!
ああ。
Right...
(シカマル)２人っきりで➡
Let's take a nice little walk...
楽しい散歩といこうぜ。
just the two of us.
(飛段)おい！
どこへ行こうってんだ!!
Hey, where are we going?
角都とオレを引き離す気か？
Are you trying to separate me
from Kakuzu?!
You...jerk!
テメエ…!!
(角都)誰もついていかなくて
いいのか？
Shouldn't someone go with him?
You're really underestimating Hidan.
飛段を見くびりすぎだ。
あのシカマルとかいう若造…。
And here that kid called Shikamaru
or whatever...
高値の賞金首になっただろうに。
would've become a bounty
of high value someday.
今日で… 死ぬぞ。
Now...
he's dead.
But your decision was the right one.
だが お前らの判断は
正しかったな。
I'm...powerful.
オレは… 強い。
お前たちとオレとでは
戦闘経験に差がありすぎる。
There's a great difference in battle experience
between you guys and myself.
お前らの額当てを見ると➡
Seeing those headbands reminds me
of the first Hidden Leaf Shinobi
I ever fought...
いちばん最初に戦った
木ノ葉の忍を思い出す。
初代 火影をな。
The First Hokage.
What?
いったい 何歳なの？ コイツ…。
How old is this guy?!
本当の不死か？
Are you really immortal?
(角都)いや そんなものは
この世に存在しない。
No. Something like that
doesn't exist in this world...
It's just that I can keep on living...
《角都 :
己の心臓が寿命で尽きる前に➡
仕留めた他者の心臓を奪い
ストックし続けることで➡
I maintain a stock by taking
the hearts of those I kill
どうにか
生きながらえてきただけだ》
before my own runs out of life...
逃がさねえってか？ ケッ！
So you won't let me get away, huh?
This shadow technique...
only lasts about five minutes, right?
この影技
５分くらいが限界なんだろ。
そして ２人きり…。
And it's just the two of us...
そりゃ
こっちも好都合なんだよ バカが！
That works out well for me, too. You idiot!
《火遁と 風遁の面が…》
The Fire Style and Wind Style masks?
(角都)オレのストックしておける
心臓は 己のを含め ５つ。
I can stock five hearts including my own...
カカシ お前に減らされたぶんは
お前の心臓をいただく。
Kakashi...
I will take your heart...
to replace the one you took from me!
(飛段)ヘヘヘッ… 条件は整った。
Everything's ready...
このときを待ってたぜ。
I've waited for this...
Die!
死ね～っ！
It appears you had no doubt
your partner would win.
But you guys really
underestimated Shikamaru.